(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-02T14:00:43.023627",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
こくよだよりのこくよだよー！
It's Kokuyo from Kokuyodayori!
はい！張り切ってこより実践中だよ！OK！
Yes! Koyori is hard at work experimenting! Okay!
今夜は数毛です 数毛お泊まり会です！
Tonight is a sumo sleepover!
はいやったー！こよりスケッチ！テデーン！はい！映え！
Yay! Koyori Sketch! Tada! Yes! Photogenic!
せーの！
Ready, set!
研究室らしい実践感！
A lab-like sense of practice!
未来の直感感 こよりの呪術 晩飯編！
Future intuition, Koyori's witchcraft dinner edition!
ヘルプ！
Help!
宮本！
Miyamoto!
思い出スクエア！
Memory Square!
こくよだよー！やったー！盛り上がろう！
It's Kokuyo! Yay! Let's get hyped!
こよネーツは特許物です 波にふたしわ空気です！
Koyonets are patented! Two wrinkles in the wave, that's air!
はい！お肉！実践！冷凍うどんは常備しています！どうですか？
Yes! Meat! Practice! Frozen udon is always stocked! How's that?
やったー！証明完了 Q.E.D！
Yay! Proof complete, Q.E.D.!
こよりには特急の作る お惣菜かな？
Is Koyori's dish made by express delivery?
いきませんね！
That won't do!
お持ちしましょう！
Let me bring it to you!
フーフーのプログラムつけてさ！
With a program to blow on it and cool it!
はい！お疲れ様！
Yes! Good job!
こくよだよー！やったー！盛り上がろう！
It's Kokuyo! Yay! Let's get hyped!
こよネーツは特許物です 波にふたしわ空気です！
Koyonets are patented! Two wrinkles in the wave, that's air!
はい！お肉！実践！冷凍うどんは常備しています！どうですか？
Yes! Meat! Practice! Frozen udon is always stocked! How's that?
はい！やったー！
Yes! Yay!
私の戦闘力は54万です！
My combat power is 540,000!
雀の涙はスチュワーデス！
A sparrow's tear is a stewardess!
ご利益包み抄造だよ！
It's a blessed paper-making wrapping!
背中まで猫背の好き！
Up to my back, a cat-like hunch!
ああ 150 50！
Ah, 150, 50!
空飛ぶものは鳥ではありません！ウンコツラーゲンス！
Things that fly are not birds! Uncotsuagens!
しっぽもふき溜めてます！
Even my tail is accumulating dust!
みんなの応援が必須だぞー！右でーす！
Everyone's support is essential! To the right!
こくよだよー！やったー！盛り上がろう！こよネーツは特許物です 波にふたしわ空気です！
It's Kokuyo! Yay! Let's get hyped! Koyonets are patented! Two wrinkles in the wave, that's air!
はい！お肉！実践！冷凍うどんは常備しています！どうですか？はい！やったー！
Yes! Meat! Practice! Frozen udon is always stocked! How's that? Yes! Yay!
せーの！こくよよ！
Ready, set! Kokuyo!
もう 君の心 チクッとしちゃえ
Just give your heart a little poke...
WAO!!
「絶対 無理」 想い付いちゃうし
Thinking "There's no way," right away,
だって だって 不安 に なる し
'Cause, 'cause, I start feeling so unsure,
全然 嘘 付け ない し
And I can never tell a single lie,
だって だって バカ 真っ直ぐ だ し
'Cause, 'cause, I'm just a fool head-on.
目指す キラキラ も きっと ぼく 次第 だ
The glittering dream I aim for is up to me.
ビター? ギブアップ なんて 言わ ない ん だ から
Bitter? Giving up? I won't say things like that!
じっ と し て ら ん ない し
I just can't stay still,
だって だって 動い ちゃう 脚
'Cause, 'cause, my legs just start moving.
1, 1, ステップアップ
1, 1, step up,
ちょっと ずつ 進め ば 夢 の 式 解け ちゃう の
Advancing bit by bit solves the equation of dreams.
なりたい ぼく を きみ が 好き な ぼく を
The me I want to be, the me you love,
ちゃんと 余り なく 魅せ たい の
I want to show you completely, without fail.
あっ ちゃう ちっちゃう
Ah, wait, oops...
びっくり する ほど できない じゃん
I can't even do it surprisingly well.
間違っ て 悩ん だり ばっかり じゃん
I just keep making mistakes and worrying.
けど きみ に 見つけ て ほしく て
But I want you to find me,
ぼく は きみ を 迎え に 行く ん だ
So I'm going out to welcome you.
出会え た なら ハッピー
If we can meet, it's happy!
わーお わーお だ 叫ん じゃえ
Wao! Wao! Just shout it out!
泣い て 吠え て 愛し て 尻尾 振っ て
Cry, howl, love, and wag your tail!
わーお わーお だ 叫ん じゃえ
Wao! Wao! Just shout it out!
だめ な ぼく を どうか 覚え て おい て
Please remember this clumsy me.
もう きみ の 心 チクッ と し ちゃえ
Just give your heart a little poke...
もう 君の心 チクッとしちゃえ
もう どう しよ とか
Wondering what to do next,
たまに 想い ちっちゃっ て 沈ん だり
Sometimes getting lost in thought and sinking down,
案外 いける かも ん わり
Thinking maybe we can pull it off,
ふわり 浮かん じゃっ て 元通り
Floating right back up as usual.
ベター リ が やめ られ ない
I just can't quit being better,
おすわり って それ なん だ っけ?
'Sit'? What was that again?
うっかり が 止め られ ない
I just can't stop being clumsy,
また 歩い て 棒 に 当たる の
Walking on and hitting a snag again.
1, 1, ステップアップ
1, 1, step up,
死ん だ ふり し てる の やめ て
Stop pretending you're dead!
はい こっち おい て
Come on over here,
欲しがる きみ と あげ すぎ な ぼく と で
Between needy you and overly generous me,
もっと いける 気 が し て い ます
I feel like we can go even further.
あっ ちゃう ちっちゃう
Ah, wait, oops...
びっくり する ほど できない じゃん
I can't even do it surprisingly well.
間違っ て 悩ん だり ばっかり じゃん
I just keep making mistakes and worrying.
けど きみ に 見つけ て ほしく て
But I want you to find me,
ぼく は きみ を 迎え に 行く ん だ
So I'm going out to welcome you.
出会え た なら ハッピー
If we can meet, it's happy!
だって
'Cause...
やっぱり ひとり じゃ だめ だ けど
Being all alone just doesn't work, though.
集まっ て ばか し て わ おっ ちゃう ば
If we gather, act silly, and go 'Wao!',
ほら いつ でも 言える 「おかえり」
Look, we can always say "Welcome back."
ぼく は きみ に 伝え たい ん だ
I want to convey this to you.
大いなる ハッピー
A grand happy!
わーお わーお だ 叫ん じゃえ
Wao! Wao! Just shout it out!
泣い て 吠え て 愛し て 尻尾 振っ て
Cry, howl, love, and wag your tail!
わーお わーお だ 叫ん じゃえ
Wao! Wao! Just shout it out!
だめ な ぼく を どうか 覚え て おい て
Please remember this clumsy me.
加速 メラメラ で ぶっ ちぎる 次第 です
Accelerating ablaze, blowing past the rest.
はぐれ ず に 希望 へ 大 爆走
Full speed ahead toward hope without straying.
もう 君の心 チクッとしちゃえ
Just give your heart a little poke...
いい じゃん ハッピー じゃん
Ain't it great? Ain't it happy?
はーい！
Hi there!
みんな、こくよー！
Everyone, hello!
ホロライブ 6期生、ホロックスの 博衣こよりだよー！
I'm Hakui Koyori from Hololive 6th Generation, Holox!
すっごい緊張しちゃった！
I was so nervous!
ということで、みんな、こくよー！
And so, everyone, hello!
博衣こより生誕Live 2025にお越しください、ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to Hakui Koyori's Birthday Live 2025!
ということで、ここでみんなにめでたいことを2つお知らせさせていただきます！
And so, I have two celebratory announcements to share with everyone!
まずは…！
First...
博衣こより誕生日を迎えましたー！わーい！
Hakui Koyori's birthday has arrived! Yay!
いやめでたく無事に迎えることができました！みんな待っていてくれてありがとー！
Yes, I was safely able to welcome it! Thank you all for waiting for me!
そして2つ目は…！
And second...
ファーストアルバムが…
My first album is...
ライブになりました！
We're live!
うわぁい！うわぁい！うわぁい！
Yay! Yay! Yay!
ということでですね、本日は
So today,
このファーストアルバムをみんなにいっぱいお届けできるような、
to deliver this first album as much as possible to everyone,
そんな音楽ライブを作りたいと思いまして、
I wanted to create a music live concert like this!
中には生演奏コーナーもご用意してますよ！
We also have a live band corner prepared for you!
生演奏、生演奏支援でしていただきます。
They'll support us with live instruments.
一緒に歌ってくださるみお先輩もあっちの方で待ってます(笑) ひそかに待っていただいております。
Mio-senpai, who'll sing with me, is waiting over there haha... waiting quietly.
みお、みお、みおしゃの気配がしますね！はい、ということで、やめると！ありがとー！
I can sense Mio... Mio-sha's presence! Yeah, so, stop it! Thank you!
まだ見えないです。まだ見えないの。まだ待ってくれてます。
You can't see her yet. You still can't see her. She's still waiting.
そしてですね、今回音楽ライブにするぞということで、ステージもなんとかっこよくしてもらえました！いぇーい！
And this time, since it's a music live, the stage got made so cool too! Yay!
こちらですね、こよりらしく、これインジェンヌっていうんですけど、まあ別になくてもいいんですけど、
Over here, in true Koyori fashion—this is called "ingénue," though you don't really need to remember that—
インジェンヌっていう化合物がね、花を浮かべてたりとかする、巨大モニター！なんとこのモニターですね、変形もしちゃうので、
a giant monitor where compounds called ingénues have flowers floating in them! And this monitor actually transforms too,
この後の曲も楽しみにしていてください！
so please look forward to the songs coming up!
そしてですね、すでにね新表情をちょこちょこっと出ております。
And new facial expressions are already showing up little by little.
その新表情もね、すごい、あの、ニュアンス変わってますみたいな感じなんだけど、
These new expressions have a really, you know, different nuance to them,
いっぱいパシャパシャとスクショ撮って、ね、ハッシュタグ「博衣こより生誕ライブ2025」で、
so please take lots of screenshots and tweet them with the hashtag #HakuiKoyoriBirthdayLive2025!
いっぱい呟いてください！呟け！トレンド1位にしろ！よろしくお願いします！
Tweet a lot! Tweet! Make it #1 on trending! Thank you!
それでは、次の曲、いきますー！
And now, let's go to the next song!
デコレート / 作詩・作曲・編曲：かいりきベア
[Song: Decorate / Lyrics, Music, Arrangement: Kairiki Bear]
変哲も無い素体 賢さ・名誉を ノートへお点々
Unremarkable subject, noting down cleverness and honor with dots...
夕暮れ 焦げた感触で 瞳を閉じて いやいやいやいや
Closing my eyes with the scorched feeling of twilight, no no no no
零れ落ちる見栄 あっちゃけない ピンク色のハイライト 点々点
Spilled pride that shouldn't be there, a pink highlight, dot dot dot
戸惑いも羽ばいた欲も 上手に誤魔化して 3年疾走 疾走 疾走
Skillfully brushing off confusion and soaring desires, running for 3 years, run, run, run
p-w いっぱい言いたいことあるんでしょう 感情も切り替えて
p-w, you have lots you want to say, right? Switch your emotions too
今だ古びた肉体でいよう
Let's stay in this worn-out body for now
零れ落ちる見栄 あっちゃけない ピンク色のハイライト 点々点
Spilled pride that shouldn't be there, a pink highlight, dot dot dot
戸惑いも羽ばいた欲も 上手に誤魔化して 3年疾走 疾走 疾走
Skillfully brushing off confusion and soaring desires, running for 3 years, run, run, run
それっていったい それっていったい それっていったい こんなんでしょう
What on earth is that, what on earth is that, is it really like this?
手探りで効く代わり
Instead of fumbling around for effects
それっていったい それっていったい それっていったい こんなんでしょう
What on earth is that, what on earth is that, is it really like this?
まして猫被るあたり それも私
Especially acting all innocent, that's me too
最期どう 中身ブスっぽいけど ポジティブ愛シャドウ 待て待て
How's the very end? Inside I look plain, but with positive eye shadow, wait wait
零れ落ちる見栄 あっちゃけない ピンク色のハイライト 点々点
Spilled pride that shouldn't be there, a pink highlight, dot dot dot
戸惑いも羽ばいた欲も 上手に誤魔化して 3年疾走 疾走 疾走
Skillfully brushing off confusion and soaring desires, running for 3 years, run, run, run
それっていったい それっていったい それっていったい こんなんでしょう 誰もしれっと私
What on earth is that, what on earth is that, is it really like this? Everyone nonchalantly... me?
愛情も切り替えて
Switch your affection too
今だ古びた楽園でいよう
Let's stay in this worn-out paradise for now
零れ落ちる見栄 あっちゃけない ピンク色のハイライト 点々点
Spilled pride that shouldn't be there, a pink highlight, dot dot dot
戸惑いも羽ばいた欲も 上手に誤魔化して 3年疾走 疾走 疾走
Skillfully brushing off confusion and soaring desires, running for 3 years, run, run, run
それっていったい それっていったい それっていったい こんなんでしょう
What on earth is that, what on earth is that, is it really like this?
手探りで効く代わり 手頃で酷くなりがわり
Instead of fumbling around, getting conveniently worse
それっていったい それっていったい それっていったい こんなんでしょう
What on earth is that, what on earth is that, is it really like this?
まして猫被るあたり それも私
Especially acting all innocent, that's me too
涙、涙、何回噛み砕り
Tears, tears, chewed up how many times,
金を鳴らせばこの通り
if you ring the bell, it's just like this,
これは救済なんだ
this is salvation.
レクイエム
Requiem
lonely ロリロリ神、降臨
Lonely, the loli god descends,
鐘を鳴らせばこの通り
By ringing the bell, here is the path,
これは救済のレクイエム
This is the requiem of salvation.
せーのっ
On three!
触ったら逮捕!極chu❤de!点呼!
You're touched, you're arrested! Extreme census with a kiss!
いちにーさんしー?
One, two, three?
ごめんなさーい
(Sorry)
ハァ?ごめんなさいが、聞こえなーい
Huh? I cannot hear your apology.
粛聖!!ロリ神レクイエム☆
Loli god requiem ☆
将来は お前なんかに
In the future, I don't want to be liked
好かれたくない
by people like you.
泥水で 口を洗え
Wash your mouth out with muddy water!
法廷で 会おう?❤
Shall we meet in court? ♡
さあ おまわりさん 連れて行って
Come on, officer, take him away!
妄想しか取り柄のない かわいそうな人
A pitiful person with nothing but delusions.
ういちゃん!ういちゃん!待ってよおういちゃん!
Ui-chan! Ui-chan! Wait for us, Ui-chan!
その姿親に見せられますかぁ?
Can you show that appearance to your parents?
こよちゃん!こよちゃん!かわいいよぉ~!
Koyo-chan! Koyo-chan! So cute!
わぁ、ありがとう、お疲れ様です~~
Wow, thank you! Good job everyone~~
ロリロリ神、降臨
The loli god descends,
マジヤバ奴等に用心
Beware of those dangerous types,
まともじゃないなら
If you aren't normal,
早く消えてください
Disappear quickly, please.
ロリロリ神、降臨
The loli god descends,
鐘を鳴らせばこの通り
By ringing the bell, here is the path,
とても優しくて 素敵なお兄ちゃん
A very kind and wonderful big brother,
楽園でホラ ねんねしな
Don't sleep in paradise...
ほら、世の中にはこんなに気持ち悪い人たちが蔓延ってるんです!
Look, in this world, there are so many disgusting people spreading!
みんな、晒しageますよ。
Everyone, let's expose them.
触ったら逮捕!極chu❤de!点呼!
You're touched, you're arrested! Extreme census with a kiss!
いちにーさんしー?
One, two, three?
ごめんなさーい
(Sorry)
ハァ?ごめんなさいが、聞こえなーい
Huh? I cannot hear your apology.
粛聖!!ロリ神レクイエム☆
Loli god requiem ☆
はぁーい、獄中にいるみなさーん
Hi everyone in prison,
刑務所ファンミーティングのお時間でぇーす
It's time for the prison fan meeting!
その、腐りきった耳をゴリゴリかっぽじって、よぉーく聴いてくださいねぇ
Open wide your rotten ears and listen carefully!
ざぁーこ(助かる~ぅ)
Trash (It helps~)
キモキモ(助かる~ぅ)
Creepy (It helps~)
うるさい(助かる~ぅ)
Noisy (It helps~)
黙っててもらっていいですか?
Can you stay silent?
嫌いです(助かる~ぅ)
I hate you (It helps~)
かわいいそ(助かる~ぅ)
So pitiful (It helps~)
だぁーきっ よぉーあっ
Love you so much~
みっともな~w
Pathetic~ lol
どうしようもない お兄ちゃんお姉ちゃん
You useless big brothers and sisters,
もう希望ない ゴミおめーら
You're already trash with no hope.
汚物消毒 110番
Garbage disinfection, emergency call 110.
固有結界 は・つ・ど・う
Reality marble, activate!
粛聖・ういビーム
Sacred ui beam!
もういっちょ!・ういビーム
One more time! Ui beam!
もっともっと!・ういビーム
Again and again! Ui beam!
ういビーム
Ui beam!
怒りの日。血の雨が降り注いだインターネットに。
The day of anger. The day when a rain of blood poured on the internet.
腐りきった意味のないゴミを浄化する、一筋の光。それが、ういビーム。
A single ray of light purifying the rotten, meaningless trash. This is the ui beam.
「うい、全てを許します……」
"Ui will forgive everything..."
ああ、この世の醜さを集めて描いてみるよ
Ah, I will gather the ugliness of this world and paint it.
真っ白なキャンバスが 汚れて泣いている
The pure white canvas is soiled and crying.
振り返った少女は、そっと手を掴む
The girl who turned around gently takes my hand.
「楽園など無いから」
"Because there is no paradise."
大きなお友達のみんなえ
To all big friends out there,
お前らが打ち込んでいるキャラには、何の意味があるの?
What is the meaning of the characters you're obsessed with?
ねえ、教えてよ。こよ、ぜんぜーんわかんないんだ!
Hey, tell me. Koyo doesn't understand at all!
ロリロリ神、降臨
The loli god descends,
さよなら笑顔でバイバイ
Goodbye with a smile,
ピリオドをどうぞ
Here is your period.
かまってでまして差し上げてゆ
I'll give you some attention.
ロリロリ神、降臨
The loli god descends,
鐘を鳴らせばこの通り
By ringing the bell, here is the path,
とても優しくて 素敵なお兄ちゃん
A very kind and wonderful big brother,
楽園でホラ ねんねしな
Don't sleep in paradise,
それが救済のレクイエム
This is the requiem of salvation.
せーのっ
On three!
触ったら逮捕!極chu❤de!点呼!
You're touched, you're arrested! Extreme census with a kiss!
いちにーさんしー?
One, two, three?
ごめんなさーい
(Sorry)
ハァ?ごめんなさいが、聞こえなーい
Huh? I cannot hear your apology.
粛聖!!ロリ神レクイエム☆
Loli god requiem ☆
ほんっーとに、きもちわるい。
Really, it's really disgusting.
この世の醜さを 集めて描いてみるよ
I will gather the ugliness of this world and paint it,
真っ白なキャンバスが 汚れて泣いている
The pure white canvas is soiled and crying.
振り向いた少女は そっと手を掴む
The girl who turned around gently takes my hand,
「楽園など無いから」
"Because there is no paradise."
大きなお友達のみんなえ
To all big friends out there,
お前らが打ち込んでいるキャラには、何の意味があるの?
What is the meaning of the characters you're obsessed with?
ねえ、教えてよ。こよ、ぜんぜーんわかんないんだ!
Hey, tell me. Koyo doesn't understand at all!
ロリロリ神、降臨
The loli god descends,
さよなら笑顔でバイバイ
Goodbye with a smile,
ピリオドをどうぞ
Here is your period.
かまってでまして差し上げてゆ
I'll give you some attention.
ロリロリ神、降臨
The loli god descends,
鐘を鳴らせばこの通り
By ringing the bell, here is the path,
とても優しくて 素敵なお兄ちゃん
A very kind and wonderful big brother,
楽園でホラ ねんねしな
Don't sleep in paradise,
それが救済のレクイエム
This is the requiem of salvation.
せーのっ
On three!
触ったら逮捕!極chu❤de!点呼!
You're touched, you're arrested! Extreme census with a kiss!
いちにーさんしー?
One, two, three?
ごめんなさーい
(Sorry)
ハァ?ごめんなさいが、聞こえなーい
Huh? I cannot hear your apology.
粛聖!!ロリ神レクイエム☆
Loli god requiem ☆
ほんっーとに、きもちわるい。
Really, it's really disgusting.
レクイエム
Requiem
せーのっ
On three!
触ったら逮捕!極chu❤de!点呼!
You're touched, you're arrested! Extreme census with a kiss!
いちにーさんしー?
One, two, three?
ごめんなさーい
(Sorry)
ハァ?ごめんなさいが、聞こえなーい
Huh? I cannot hear your apology.
粛聖!!ロリ神レクイエム☆
Loli god requiem ☆
ほんっーとに、きもちわるい。
Really, it's really disgusting.
ういちゃーん！
Ui-chan!
え、こよ？
Eh, Koyo?
ういちゃーん！
Ui-chan!
え、だれ？
Eh, who?
こよりにゃーんちゃんだよ！
It's Koyorinyan-chan!
わぁ、どうも。
Oh, hello.
あ、あのさようなら
Ah, um, goodbye.
あ、ういびーむ、あ、ちょっと待って！
Ah, Ui-beam, ah, wait a minute!
ういびーむ、てる？
Is the Ui-beam shining?
照ってないです、さようなら。
It's not shining, goodbye.
あ、ちょっと待って！もういっかい！
Ah, wait a minute! One more time!
なんですか？
What is it?
あの角度を変えて目で見てもらえる…
Um, can you look at it from another angle...
やばくしんじゃだ…
Dangerous believer...
ういちゃーん！この後おねえちゃんとじに…
Ui-chan! After this, with big sister...
行って欲しくっ…
I wanted you to go...
え、お誕生日プレゼントにドビういちゃん貰えるんじゃない！？
Eh, can't I get a Dobi Ui-chan as a birthday present!?
なぁ お家にまで帰っていいんじゃないの？
Hey, isn't it okay to go home already?
うわー
Waaah!
おい、のりまお先生や。何してんの？
Hey, Norimao-sensei. What are you doing?
あれ？さっきまでロリじゃなかったですか？
Huh? Weren't you a loli just a second ago?
いやいやいや
No, no, no,
私か...
I'm cu...
あれ、今、今すれ違わなかったですか？可愛い。
Huh, didn't we just pass each other? So cute.
え、誰々？知らない知らない。
Eh, who? Who? I don't know, I don't know.
知らない、誰、誰はおかしいでしょ。
You don't know? Who, who is weird.
いや、誰って、田中も幼女でしょ。よーよーよーよー...
No, who? Tanaka's a loli too. Yo-yo-yo-yo...
え、ていうか何？何その姿は？
Eh, I mean what? What is that appearance?
え？あ、今お話...
Eh? Ah, right now we're talking...
ロリ神やってじゃないですか！
We're doing Loli Kami Requiem!
え、恥ずかしいよ！
Eh, how embarrassing!
え、だって、ロリ神恥ずかしいよ。
Eh, because Loli Kami is embarrassing.
これ自分だって付けてた... つけててえ何？
You were wearing this yourself... Wearing it, eh, what?
え、外してきたから？
Eh, because you took it off?
あれ？記憶これ共有されないタイプなのか？
Huh? Is this memory not shared between types?
え、なになになに言ってるんだろ。
Eh, what on earth is she saying?
え、一人になっとった。
Eh, I ended up all alone.
みんな！こんにちは！
Everyone! Hello!
私が乗っ取ったよ！
I've taken over!
乗っ取んな！
Don't take over!
はーい！乗っ取ってきましたよ！
Yeees! I've taken over!
いや、こよちゃんもちょっとショウキード見てたから忘れちゃってたけど。
Well, Koyochian was watching Shoki-D, so she forgot, but...
あ、誕生日おめでとう！
Ah, happy birthday!
やった！ありがとうございます！
Yay! Thank you very much!
そう、誕生日ガールです。
That's right, I'm the birthday girl.
誕生日ガール、大丈夫？1人ずつ喋ってて。いやいやいや、壊すぎ、1人でじゃないよ。
Birthday girl, are you okay? Talking one by one. No no no, too scary, not by yourself.
いたんだよ、さっきまでロリゆるちゃんが。
She was here, Loli Yuru-chan until just now.
まぼろしみたいな。
Like a phantom.
ロリゆるちゃんはいるんだ！いたもん！
Loli Yuru-chan is here! She was here!
じゃあなんかしてたのさっき2人で。
Then what were you two doing just now?
あ、そうなんです。あの吉っさんの作ったね、みゅなみゅねクインも一緒に歌って踊っていたわけですよ。
Ah, that's right. We were singing and dancing together to Myuna Myune Queen, which Yossan made.
そうなんだ、私とは何もしてくれないってわけ？え？え？
Is that so? Does that mean you won't do anything with me? Eh? Eh?
え、したけど... え、してない、してない、してない。
Eh, we did... Eh, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't.
え、でもでもでもでも、それは歌って踊ってくれるってこと？
Eh, but but but but, does that mean you'll sing and dance?
え、もちろん。何のために来たと思ってんの？
Eh, of course. What do you think I came here for?
え、やった！もう一曲やってくれるんだ、嬉しい！一曲...
Eh, yay! You'll do another song, I'm so happy! One song...
いや、まだ一曲しか... ややこしいな。
No, only one song so far... How confusing.
ややこしいな。じゃあなんですけど。
How confusing. Well then.
あの、この前ね、こよりが息継ぎでしまったこつまつの時に、
Um, the other day, when Koyori was running out of breath during Kotsumatsu,
なんかこよちゃんの新曲結構聞いててって、私ってくれてたじゃないですか。
you were listening to Koyochian's new song a lot, and you said you listened to it, right?
おかしい。オタクの配信見ないで！
Weird. Don't watch otaku streams!
アーカイブも全部見たよ。最初から最後まで見たから。
I watched all the archives too. I watched from start to finish.
や、恥ずかしい！じゃあ、あの曲、あの曲をお願いしてもいいですか？
Yay, how embarrassing! Well then, can I ask for that song, that song?
歌っていただけてもいいんですか？もちろんですよ！もうやる気満々じゃないな。
Can you sing it for me? Of course! You're full of enthusiasm.
いや、練習しましたから！一緒にやったもんね、ですね。
No, because I practiced! We did it together, right? That's right.
ということでね、こちらはまなんだにお出かけいただいた楽曲、シアワセこーりにも一緒に歌って踊っちゃいまーす！いえーい！
So, the song we went out to learn here as well, Shiawase Koronium, let's sing and dance together! Yay!
じゃあ3番。やるやるやる！
Then number 3. Let's do it, let's do it, let's do it!
コヨチャン チュキ チュキ
Koyochian, chuuki, chuuki,
みんなの脳みそに お注射しちゃうぞ～！
I'm gonna give everyone's brains an injection~!
実験だ！実験だ！実験！実験！実験だ！
Experiment! Experiment! Experiment, experiment, experiment!
実験だ！実験だ！ (うお～～っふー！)
Experiment! Experiment! (Woaah-hoo!)
研究 研究 研究 耐久 回 急上昇中
Research, research, research, endurance rounds soaring up,
呼ばれて飛び出てパピブペボーム！
summoned and popping out, papipupe boom!
検証 検証 検証 caution アテンションプリーズ
Verification, verification, verification, caution, attention please,
舐めてたら火傷しちゃうヨ
if you lick it you'll get burned y'know
(マヨ！)迷ったらダメダメ
(Mayo!) If you get lost, no no
(マヨ！)真夜中サイエンス
(Mayo!) Midnight science
(マヨ！)魔除けの呪文は マヨ マヨ ちゅっちゅっ！
(Mayo!) The warding spell is mayo mayo chu-chu!
(コヨ！)今宵のデザート
(Koyo!) Tonight's dessert
(コヨ！)高揚する heart beat
(Koyo!) Exhilarating heartbeat
(コヨ！)こより こよられ 恋焦がれ～♡
(Koyo!) Koyori, Koyorare, love-stricken~♡
サイン→コサイン→タangent(ay)
Sine → Cosine → Tangent (ay)
試験管→docking→ダイレクト(ay)
Test tube → docking → direct (ay)
白衣の天使が降臨！(^_^)/ヤッホー！！
The angel in a white coat has descended! Yahoo!!
天才 天才 天才 とんでもなく偉い
Genius, genius, genius, unbelievably great,
崇めちゃってOK 褒めてくスタイル
worshiping is OK, the style of praising,
最高 最高 最高 そんでラブって優勝
highest, highest, highest, and loving is victory
ぶっちゃけ脳内シュワシュワ スタンディングオベーション
Honestly, fizzing in my brain, standing ovation
(Wow-o-o-o) 科学とは 爆発だ
(Wow-o-o-o) Science is an explosion!
ポッチとピポパ 間違えてドッカーン
Potchi and pipopa, making a mistake and dokkaan,
ドジなトコも計算通りよ
even my clumsy sides are according to plan
実験だ！実験だ！実験！実験！実験だ！
Experiment! Experiment! Experiment, experiment, experiment!
実験だ！実験だ！ (うお～～っふー！)
Experiment! Experiment! (Woaah-hoo!)
さぁーて 早速始めましょう！ これより行うは 天才マッドサイエンティストと
Now then, let's start right away! What we will conduct now is a genius mad scientist
天才イラストレーターによる 世にも奇妙な、すん～ばらしぃ 大～実験ッ！
and a genius illustrator, a bizarre, fu~n... wonderful grand experiment!
ようこそ 魅惑のラボラトリー
Welcome to the seductive laboratory
(ドキドキワクワク胸打つ鼓動)
(Thumping, throbbing, heartbeat echoing)
怖くない 大丈夫よ
It's not scary, it's okay
(ホラ ケタ ケタ カラ カラ 笑いましょう)
(Come on, let's laugh with a cackle and a chuckle)
試験管をブッ刺せば 完了
Pierce the test tube and it's complete
(ドク ドク バク バク 脈打つ脈動)
(Thumping, throbbing, pulsing pulsation)
「原子番号315番、コヨリニウム これは、シアワセになる、最高の粒子なのだかっ？」
"Atomic number 315, Koronium! Is this the ultimate particle to achieve happiness?"
病みつきになっちゃえば Eじゃん (Eじゃん！)
If you get hooked on it, isn't it great (Isn't it great!)
欲しいなら叫べば Eじゃん (Eじゃん！)
If you want it, just shout out, isn't it great (Isn't it great!)
大好きですかー？ (大好きでーす！)
Do you love it? (We love it!)
シアワセですかー？ (シアワセでーす！)
Are you happy? (We are happy!)
愛すれば救われる
If you love, you will be saved
愛せれば救われる
If you love, you'll be saved.
呻呼、なんて素敵な世界なんでしょ！
Oh, what a wonderful world!
「ほんまか？」
"Really?"
一途なその瞳で 見つめて
Gaze with those devoted eyes,
推して 萌えて 溶けちゃおんねー
Support, adore, and melt away!
明るい未来に 乾杯(^-^)v
Cheers to a bright future! (^o^)v
天才 天才 天才 はちゃめちゃに凄い！
Genius, genius, genius, insanely amazing!
祀られてOK 神ってくスタイル
Worshiped is okay, a godlike style!
最高 最高 最高 呼ばれたらずっと
The best, the best, the best, if called upon, always
本気で脳髄トロトロ スタンディングオベーション
Melting our brains in earnest, standing ovation!
(Wow-o-o-o) 人生とは爆発さ
(Wow-o-o-o) Life is an explosion!
ポチッとピポパ 間違えてドッカーン
Tap beep-boop, mistake it and BOOM!
ドジなトコも計算通りよ (計算通り)
Even my clumsy moments are all as calculated (As calculated)
計算通りよ 計算通りよ
All as calculated, all as calculated!
実験！実験！実験だ！実験だ！実験だ！
Experiment! Experiment! It's an experiment!
(うおーーーわっふー！)
(Wahoo!)
実験！実験！実験だ！実験だ！実験だ！
Experiment! Experiment! It's an experiment!
実・験・だーーーっ！！
It's an experiment!
（ミャーオ）
Meow!
ねぇねぇ私気づいてる 見えるように消しゴム落としたり
Hey hey, I notice you, dropping an eraser so you'd see,
教科書だって実は忘れてない
And I actually didn't forget my textbook either.
バレて焦ってる君は猫みたい
Panicking when caught, you're just like a cat.
全然勉強してねーわ あんなん俺でも出来ちゃうわー
"I didn't study at all! Even I could do that!"
男子ってば単純ね 愛想笑いでハイハイね
Boys are so simple, just giving polite smiles, yeah right.
変な髪型それ言うな 一いち虫とか見せんでいい！
"Don't say my hair's weird! And don't show me bugs!"
そうやって気を引くの なんとかなんないの
Trying to get my attention like that, can't you do something else?
もう遊ぶ気分じゃなくなっちゃうかもダーリン
Darling, I might not feel like playing around anymore.
かっこつけさせ担げるから キメてよね
Let me look cool and support me, so make it cool, okay?
コネコミュニケーション 噛みついちゃう予感 合図だぞ！見逃せない
Cone Communication: a hunch we'll bite each other. It's a sign! Don't miss it!
コネコミュニケーション からかうだけじゃわっかんない！聞かせてよ
Cone Communication: teasing isn't enough! Let me hear it!
飛び込んじゃお 爪立てちゃお
Let's dive in, let's show our claws!
時々は撫でられたい？
Do you want to be petted sometimes?
きっと手の平いっぱい愛で
Surely with hands full of love,
気まぐれを仕留めて！
Capture my caprice!
興味ないって言いながらこっち見てる
Saying you're not interested while looking this way,
聞こえるように好きな子の話してる
Talking about the girl you like so I can hear.
他の子と仲良しで照れ隠し
Acting close with other girls to hide your shyness,
耳立てちゃうねバカみたい！
Pricking up your ears, you look so foolish!
絆創膏とかいらねーわ 本気でやったら勝たせたわー
"I don't need bandages! If I went all out, I'd win!"
そーなんだすっごいね じゃあ最初からやっとけば？
"Oh really, that's amazing. Then why didn't you do that from the start?"
あいっ、お前が好きだって 絶対誰にも言うなって！
"Hey, I like you, so don't tell anyone ever!"
そーなんだ気になっちゃう 付き合っちゃおっかな？
"Oh really? Now I'm curious, should we go out?"
ねぇ殻を破った君も素敵よダーリン
Hey, darling, even you breaking out of your shell is wonderful.
ため息だって駆け引きね 数えてて
Even sighs are part of the game, so keep counting.
コネコミュニケーション ためらっちゃうボタン 本気だぞ！強がりたい
Cone Communication: hesitating buttons. I'm serious! I want to act tough.
コネコミュニケーション じゃれ合うたびにわっかんない！教えてよ
Cone Communication: every time we play, I don't get it! Teach me.
落ち込んじゃお 背伸びしちゃお
Let's feel down, let's stretch ourselves out,
よしよし甘えられない
There, there, I can't act spoiled.
嫉妬猫舌言いたいね 熱いのは苦手よ！
I want to say I'm a jealous cat-tongue, I hate hot things!
もう！“なんでもないわ”聞き飽きちゃったよダーリン
Geez! I'm tired of hearing "It's nothing," darling.
目配せなんてとっておきも君だけに
Even winks, my special treat, are just for you.
コネコミュニケーション 噛みついちゃう予感 合図だぞ！見逃せない
Cone Communication: a hunch we'll bite each other. It's a sign! Don't miss it!
コネコミュニケーション からかうだけじゃわっかんない！聞かせてよ
Cone Communication: teasing isn't enough! Let me hear it!
飛び込んじゃお 爪立てちゃお
Let's dive in, let's show our claws!
ドキドキ離れられない？
Thrilled and unable to part?
尻尾振るように頂戴愛
Give me love like wagging a tail,
そっぽ向きがち曖昧じゃ
Being prone to looking away and being vague
やっぱ君にはもったいないね
Is still too good for you, you know.
気が向けばあげるわ！チャオ☆
If I feel like it, I'll give it to you! Ciao☆
ピーマンだーーー！
Piman!
よかったーーー！おめでとうーーー！
That's great! Congratulations!
ありがとうーーー！おめでとうーーー！
Thank you! Congratulations!
よってくれてありがとうーーー！
Thank you for gathering!
これでありがとうって言うことで、元気に飛び出していただきました。
With that "Thank you," she came bounding out with so much energy!
去年の5月にコラボしたPii丸様ことPiiちゃんでーす！
It's Pii-chan, aka Pii-maru-sama, who collaborated with me last May!
イェーイ！
Yay!
おたきびこー！
Scream it out!
イェーイ！イェーイ！
Yay! Yay!
ということで今歌っていただいたのはPiiちゃんの新曲
So the song she just sang for us is Pii-chan's new song...
『脱法サマースダンサン』だよ！
"Dappou Summer Sundance"!
そうなんですよー！一緒に歌わせていただきました！
That's right! We got to sing it together!
かわいいかったー！やったぜ！イェーイ！
So cute! Yay! Woohoo!
この感じでねちょっとテンション高く始めたんですけど、実はですね今より何笑ってんだよ！
We started off with high energy like this, but actually... What are you laughing at?!
実はあのPiiちゃんに言いたいことが1つあるんです。
Actually, there's one thing I want to tell Pii-chan.
はい！
Yes?
なんだろう。
What is it?
え？あの前にねPiiちゃん誓いは…
Uh, before, Pii-chan made a vow...
Piiちゃんがね、去年の末ぐらいに今年懺悔したいことっていうのを配信で喋ってたんですよ。
Around the end of last year, Pii-chan streamed about something she wanted to confess this year.
え、うん。そうその時にね
Oh, yeah. Right, at that time...
もうこよりちゃんのことを猫だと思ってたんだけど、ごめんなさい！キツネだったんだねって言ってたんですよ！
"I thought Koyori-chan was a cat, but I'm sorry! She was a fox!" she said!
え、待って、キツネじゃないの？
Wait, aren't you a fox?
コヨーテだよ！
I'm a coyote!
コヨーテって何？え、コヨーテってキツネの妖怪じゃないの？え、なんで？コヨーテってキツネの妖怪…いやキツネの妖怪は九尾やろ！
A coyote? What's that? Isn't a coyote a fox yokai? Wait, why? No, a fox yokai is a nine-tailed fox!
ああー！そうか！
Ah! Right!
九尾、九尾、九尾、九尾ってこと？あ、そうそうそうそう。
You mean Kyubi, Kyubi, Kyubi? Ah, exactly, exactly.
違うんだよ！じゃあコヨーテって何？
That's not it! Then what is a coyote?
コヨーテは、コヨーテや！こよりのことや！
A coyote is a coyote! It's me, Koyori!
狼、キツネ、コヨーテみたいな感じでズレがあるんですよ。
There's this mismatch like wolf, fox, coyote.
今日だけはね、今日はこれを覚えて帰っていただければと、思っております。
I hope you'll remember this just for today when you go home.
わかった！よかった！
Understood! I'm glad!
てことでですね、ええそんなPiiちゃんと、ええ前にコラボしたときに一緒に歌いたいねって言ってた歌があるんですよね。
So, with that Pii-chan, there's a song we talked about wanting to sing together when we collaborated before.
そう！はいそのね曲を！
Yes! Right, that song!
このあともう1曲一緒に歌っちゃいたいと思います！やったー！
We'd love to sing one more song together right after this! Yay!
てことで、あのこよりが特訓してくんねえバズー！バズーしてほしい！バズー！バズー！
So, Koyori trained hard for it—Bazu! I want you to bazu! Bazu! Bazu!
え、ちょっ、それはキツネやろ！いやちょっとね白衣っぽい羽織りをきまして、次に歌うのは同じ七星管弦楽団さんのね！
Wait, that's a fox! No, wait, putting on this Hakui-style haori, the next song we're singing is by Nanahoshi Kangen Gakudan-san!
曲！一緒に歌いましょう！やったー！歌うぞ！歌うぞ！
Song! Let's sing it together! Yay! Let's sing! Let's sing!
それでは聞いてください。せーの！おとめよ求めよQ.E.D.！
Now, please listen. Ready, go! Maiden, seek for it, Q.E.D.!
乙女よ求めよQ.E.D.!!
Maiden, seek for it, Q.E.D.!!
作詞：ナナホシ管弦楽団　作曲：岩見陸
Lyrics: Nanahoshi Kangen Gakudan | Music: Riku Iwami
知りたいな
I want to know
君はさ 僕のことどう思う？
What do you think of me?
僕はね 君のこと……あとは宿題
I... think of you... and the rest is homework.
ラブ・ラボ 引きこっちゃうな？聞かなきゃってほら 相性！（実験中）
Love Lab, are you going to shut yourself in? We gotta ask, look, compatibility! (Experimenting)
論より証拠主義です 前進あるのみ！
Proof over theory is the principle, forward only!
ねえ、少し手伝って 人類の課題
Hey, help me a little, a task for mankind.
好き×好き×好き×好き×好き×好き×好き×好き×好き＝？ 答え合わせしましょう？
Like x Like x Like x Like x Like x Like x Like x Like x Like = ? Shall we check the answers?
見つけちゃう 魔法の公式 化学反応してるよね
I'll find it, the magic formula, we're having a chemical reaction.
僕ら 問題は まだまだまだまだ未解決
The problem is still, still, still, still unsolved.
証明中！ 恋の予想 物理法則 書き足しちゃおもんね（どうだ！）
Proving now! Love prediction, laws of physics, I'll add it in (How's that!)
これぞ天才だ！
This is genius!
あの子より その子より もっと好きって言ってちょうだい
More than that girl, more than that girl, tell me you like me more!
乙女よ求めよQ.E.D.!!
Maiden, seek for it, Q.E.D.!!
【Question!!】
[Question!!]
やっぱりさ さっきから僕のこと見てたよね？
I knew it, you've been watching me this whole time, haven't you?
【Question!!】
[Question!!]
見てない？じゃあ……僕が君のこと……
Not watching? Then... what if I...
ときめきパラドックス 慌てちゃって隠れちゃう？（葛藤中）
Flustered paradox, panicking and hiding? (In conflict)
宇宙も秘密主義じゃ ビッグバン！
The universe is also secretive, Big Bang!
ねえ、君とふたり 人類の終わり
Hey, just the two of us, the end of mankind.
好き×好き×好き×好き×好き×好き×好き×好き×好き ∞未来でしょ？
Like x Like x Like x Like x Like x Like x Like x Like x Like = Infinite future, right?
ときめきょう 魔法の公式 惹かれ合うたび 不思議なレポートは進行形
Fluttering magic formula, every time we're drawn together, this mysterious report is in progress.
まだまだまだまだ未検出 設計中！
Still, still, still, still undetected, designing now!
DNA 君の細胞 書き換えちゃうもんね
DNA, your cells, I'm going to rewrite them!
スバリ天才だ！
That's right, genius!
どの子より この子より ずっと好きって言ってちょうだい
More than any girl, more than this girl, tell me you love me forever!
言ってるじゃん！
You're saying it!
乙女よ求めよ Q.E.D.！
Maidens, seek it out, Q.E.D.!
好き×好き×好き×好き×好き×好き×好き×…=？
Like x like x like x like... = ?
ねぇ、僕らふたり
Hey, the two of us
人類の終わりに
at the end of humanity,
割り切れなかった あまりだったら
if there's an undivided remainder,
ねぇ、少し手伝って
hey, give me a hand,
人類の課題
humanity's problem.
好き×好き×好き×好き× 答え合わせしましょ？
Like x like x like... Let's check our answers, shall we?
見つけちゃお！魔法の公式 化学反応してるよね僕ら
Found it! Magic formula, we're having a chemical reaction, right?
問題は まだまだまだまだ 未解決
The problem is still, still, still unsolved,
証明中！恋の予測 物理法則書き足しちゃうもんね
currently proving it! Prediction of love, adding to the laws of physics!
これぞ天才だ！
This is true genius!
あの子よりこの子より もっと「好き」って言ってちょうだい
Say you like me more than that girl, more than this girl!
乙女よ求めよ Q.E.D.！
Maidens, seek it out, Q.E.D.!
3.141592653589793238462643383279502884197...7...???
……Q.E.D.!!
...Q.E.D.!!
今こそ最大 叶えましょう
Now is the time to make it the greatest, let's make it come true
史上最大のQUESTION! みんな楽しんでる？ここからは折り曲げメドレー行くよ！
The greatest QUESTION in history! Is everyone having fun? From here, it's a medley!
ドキッ心臓 メラメラ抑えられないのって レグルスなので余裕です
Thumping heart, burning uncontrollably—since I'm Regulus, it's a breeze
声を合わすの またひとつ励みよ
Matching our voices is another encouragement
謎は飲み物です Come on! Q&A!
Mysteries are drinks! Come on! Q&A!
発射こっちほら 巻き起こる ドラマティック ダイアリー実践
Launch over here, look, a dramatic diary comes alive in practice
感じてみなきゃ始まらない 元気 先生 共有 出逢う理由
Can't start without feeling it—energy, teacher, sharing, reason for meeting
一緒にどんどん少しましょう あなたと経験していくタイム
Let's gradually do more together, time experiencing with you
ぜんぶの夢 揃えて急いで 仕掛けねば次がある
Gather all dreams and hurry, or there'll be a next trick
泣いて笑っては あんな日も永遠 願いは添え
Crying and laughing, days like that are eternal, wishes attached
その胸に目を 手の親しあわせ 今以上 最大 叶えましょう
Eyes on that chest, interlocking hands, let's make it greater than ever
今以上最大叶えましょう
Let's make it greater than ever
長すぎるわ愛のホデイスティック
The hypothesis of love is way too long
達成ってあいにくなくて ダンス必要はない
Unfortunately, there's no achievement, no need to dance
不気味で綺麗で性室だって 不安定は歓迎
Eerie, beautiful, and even pure-natured—instability is welcome
片足で立って 支えていてよ 僕の正体
Stand on one leg, support my true identity
アンバランスな 僕の正体
My unbalanced true identity
初めて世界を共に刻んだ線は
The line we first carved into the world together
思い通りの光が 今すぐに飛び出していく
The light just as we imagined is about to burst out right now
羽ばたいた 忘れないでね このまぶしさを
We spread our wings, don't forget this dazzling brightness
心に満ちた輝きを追いかけて ありえない景色に たどり着きましょう
Chasing the brilliance that filled our hearts, let's reach an impossible scenery
招待ちょうだい 一生楽しもうよ シーソー
Invite me, let's enjoy forever, seesaw
壊すほどめいっぱい 戯れて居場所を探すの
Playing to the point of breaking, searching for a place to belong
傷は日常 なんてしょう 答えのないよ 最後まで
Wounds are everyday life, huh? Without an answer, until the very end
行きそうにやりたいことなくて 楽しく手を振ってらしくいたい苦しいなんて
With nothing I desperately want to do, waving happily, wanting to be myself, even if it hurts
いやだわ すぐなり 振り返り 回そう明日へ
No way, turn around right away, let's spin towards tomorrow
わがままな夢もっとお菓子を
A selfish dream, more sweets
涙越えてゆけ for luck, for luck, for luck!!
Cross over tears for luck, for luck, for luck!!
ねえ鏡の中
Hey, inside the mirror,
無理な笑顔に唇噛む
biting my lip at a forced smile.
ひとりよがりだとわかってる
I know I'm being selfish,
自信をなくして崩れ落ちたとき
when I lost confidence and collapsed.
ああキミの声がしたんだ
Ah, I heard your voice.
キミだけのヒーローでありたい
Wanting to be your sole hero.
悔しさを重ねて駆け上がっていこうね
Let's climb up piling up our regrets!
今はまだ未知の途中
We are still on the unknown path...
きっと
Surely...
ぜったい！
Absolutely!
もっと！めいっぱい！まだまだ明日を目指して
More! To the fullest! Still aiming for tomorrow,
天よんでぐんぐん！まだまだ夢の向こうへ
Soaring high into the skies! Still beyond our dreams.
no way どんな難題だっていいのさ ベストアンサーで弾き返せ
No way, whatever difficult problem, bounce it back with the best answer.
へこたれたって最後まで全身全霊
Even if I get discouraged, with all my heart until the end.
３！２！１でfly high!! どんなに遠くたってぼくたちは諦めない
3, 2, 1 and fly high!! No matter how far, we won't give up.
涙んだって越えてゆくんだ ほら ほら ほら
We will overcome even tears, look, look, look,
いま いま sweet one more time!
now, now, sweet one more time!
ぼくだけじゃない きみだけじゃない
Not just me, not just you.
きみだけじゃない
Not just you.
悔しくて嫌いになった
I grew to hate it out of frustration,
消してしまいたいと思った
and wished I could just erase it.
だから聞こえないように叫ぶ歌
So I sing a song shouted so it won't be heard,
水たまりに吐き捨てた声
a voice spat out into a puddle.
水たまり 作詞・作曲 Carlos.K
[Song: Mizutamari / Lyrics & Music: Carlos.K]
この感情はなんなんだろう 素直に受け入れられないよ
What is this emotion? I can't accept it honestly.
息もできないほどに押し潰されてく
I'm being crushed to the point of suffocation.
ああ 誰かの眩しさに焦って 待ってなんて生きづらい なんで
Ah, rushing at someone else's brilliance—waiting is so hard to live, why?
唇を噛み締めた
I bit my lip hard.
乾いた心に震わぬ想いが溜まる
Unshakable feelings pile up in a dry heart.
水面に映ったこの顔は嘘つきだ
This face reflected on the water's surface is a liar.
聞いて
Listen,
綺麗じゃない綺麗じゃないでも綺麗じゃない綺麗じゃないでしょ まっすぐにぶきようでもいい
Not pretty, not pretty, but it's not pretty, right? Even if I'm straight and clumsy, it's fine.
どうでもいいどうでもいいんだよ 君を覆うそんな雨も水たまり踏みつけて
It doesn't matter, it really doesn't. Stomp over the puddles and the rain covering you.
流れちゃっていいんだ
It's okay if it flows away,
溢れてたっていいんだから
it's okay if it overflows.
恐れずに前を向いたら
If you look ahead without fear,
息をしてみせて
try taking a breath.
誰かの物語に生きて
Living in someone else's story,
自分が主役じゃないなんて
knowing you're not the protagonist...
わかってるいい声演じれば
I know, playing a good voice
それでいいわけないよね
isn't enough, right?
本音は大嫌い そんな自分が大嫌いだ
I truly hate my true feelings, I hate myself like that.
砂漠に降りつづける雨
Rain keeps falling on the desert,
傘もささずに
without even opening an umbrella,
隠した涙は
The hidden tears
誰にもわからないでしょう
probably nobody will ever know.
聞いて くだらない くだらない
Listen, it's so pointless, so pointless
このあらすじは破り捨てたい かき変える運命を
I want to tear up this synopsis, rewrite destiny.
からっぽな話を笑顔にしてさよならと伝えたんだ
I turned the empty story into a smile and said goodbye.
もうここには戻らない
I won't return here anymore.
綺麗じゃない綺麗じゃなくても
Even if it's not pretty, even if you hate it,
嫌いじゃない嫌いじゃないでしょ 真っ直ぐに不器用でもいい
even if you don't hate it, being straightforwardly clumsy is fine too.
どうでもいいどうでもいいんだよ
It doesn't matter, it really doesn't matter,
君をそんな雨の水たまり見つけて
finding you in that rainy puddle,
笑われてたっていいんだ
It's okay if we're laughed at,
溢れてたっていいんだから
it's okay if it overflows.
恐れずに前を向いたら
If you look ahead without fear,
息をしてみせて
try taking a breath.
はい、ということで！
And there you have it!
ふー！歌えたー！
Woo! We sang it!
ちょっと緊張したかも
I might have been a bit nervous.
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
てことでですね、今回は生演奏とえー、ピアノでさせていただいたんですけども
So this time, we performed with live accompaniment and piano...
こりはね、ミオ先輩のしっとりした歌声が大好きなので一緒に歌いたいなと思ってお呼びしちゃいました！
I love Mio-senpai's emotional singing voice, so I invited her because I wanted to sing together!
ありがとう！こよのね可愛い声もさ、なんかいろんな、かっこいい歌声もあったりさ
Thank you! Koyori's cute voice has various cool singing voices too,
さっきも聴いてたんだけど
and I was listening earlier...
嬉しい！うれしい本当に上手だったよなー
I'm so happy! You were really good.
ミオ先輩にそう言ってもらえると嬉しすぎじゃう
Hearing Mio-senpai say that makes me too happy!
そしてですね、素敵な演奏はウイングさんにしていただいております
And also, the wonderful performance is by Wing-san.
素敵！すごい！響き渡りますね
Wonderful! Amazing! It echoes so beautifully.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
はい、ということで二人で歌うのは
Yes, so for singing together as a duo...
あのフェスの「アニマル」とか、あとミオ先輩の4周年の「夜もすがら君を想う」
That Fes 'Animal', and Mio-senpai's 4th anniversary 'Yomosugara Kimi o Omou'...
歌ったね！こうやってしっとり、ガチしっとりは初めてだったよね？
We sang those! Doing a genuinely emotional song like this was a first, right?
初めてでしたね！
It was our first!
いやあ、楽しかったです。なかなかこういう機会をね、生演奏でっていうのは
Yeah, it was fun. You don't often get opportunities like this with live accompaniment...
いただけないからちょっと嬉しかったでも！呼んでくれてありがとう！
I was a bit happy though! Thanks for inviting me!
呼んでくれて嬉しい！本当にお忙しい中ありがとう！
Thanks for inviting me! Thank you so much!
もう今日めちゃくちゃ長時間のほら待たせてるんで
You've been waiting for such a long time today,
こよの誕生日を祝えてよかったよ！
I'm so glad we could celebrate Koyori's birthday!
よかった！そして無事に歌えてよかったー！体調もね、色々整えてきてね
I'm so glad! And I'm so glad we sang safely! I adjusted my physical condition...
本当に今日やっと歌えるようになってすごいなって
I think it's amazing you were able to sing today at last.
よかったよ！一緒に歌えました無事！
I'm so glad! We sang together safely!
はい、じゃあね、この後ももうちょっと続くみたいだから
Yes, well, it seems like there's a bit more to come after this...
うちはね、ここらでちょっとお暇をしようかなって思います。
I think I'll take my leave around here.
ありがとうございます！じゃあ頑張ってね！見守ってるから！じゃあね！
Thank you! Do your best! I'm watching over you! Bye!
お疲れ様でした...よし、補給させていただきまして、生演奏パートもう一曲歌わせていただきたいと思いまーす
Good work... Alright, having recharged, I'd like to sing one more song in the live accompaniment part...
次の曲は、2回目の作詞に挑戦して、みんなへの...
The next song, I challenged myself with lyric writing for the second time, for everyone...
思いを込めた曲です。
This song is filled with my feelings.
ファーストアルバムから聞いてください。
Please listen to it from my first album.
Dear you
ねぇもしも ねぇもしも
Hey, what if... Hey, what if...
くらくて孤独に 飲まれそうな夜
On a dark night that feels like it will swallow you in solitude,
ソファで独り膝抱え ちっぽけさ感じてた
Hugging my knees alone on the sofa, I felt so small.
強いよね 見られがち ほんとは弱いのに
People see me as strong, even though I'm really weak.
不器用で負けず嫌い 甘えられないから
I'm clumsy, hate losing, and can't rely on others,
誰にも言えないままの ぼくの弱さに
To my weakness that I can't tell anyone about,
キミだけが手を差し伸べてくれたんだ
You were the only one who reached out a hand.
一緒に笑って 一緒に悔しんで
Laughing together, feeling frustrated together,
そんな日々がかけがえない宝物
Days like that are irreplaceable treasures.
一生こんな日が続いていくように
Hoping days like this will last a lifetime,
ぼくにできることはなんだってしたいよ
I want to do whatever I can do for you.
ねぇもしも ねぇもしも
Hey, what if... Hey, what if...
キミがぼくを忘れちゃっても
Even if you were to forget me,
キミの中にぼくの生きざまが
My way of life inside of you
かすかでも残って
Will remain, even faintly,
キミがね いるから
Because you're here,
強くなれるよ
I can become strong.
不安も辛さも一緒なら 乗り越えられるんだ
If we share our anxiety and pain, we can overcome them.
一緒に泣いて 一緒に前を向いて
Crying together, looking forward together,
キミといると嫌いなとこも愛せる
When I'm with you, I can love the parts of myself I hate.
一生一緒だなんて言っても 叶うかなんて誰にも分からないけど
Even if we say 'together forever', no one knows if it'll come true, but...
ねぇキミにねぇずっと 好きでいてほしいワガママかな
Hey, I want you to keep loving me forever... Is that too selfish?
すべて夢を叶える日まで
Until the day all our dreams come true,
一緒に笑って 一緒に前を向いて
Laughing together, looking forward together,
ずっとキミの隣にいられますように
Hoping I can stay by your side forever.
キミが好きでいてくれるのならぼくはここにいるよ
If you want me here, I'll be right here.
ねぇこれも夢だよ
Hey, even this is a dream.
ねぇすべて叶うかな
Hey, will all of them come true?
ねぇキミに ありがとう
Hey, thank you so much.
声を合図に
With our voices as the signal,
Parade, Parade, Parade!
探していく
We go searching for it.
スタートは何度だって
No matter how many times we start over,
ただ 独り言 綴った
I simply muttered to myself.
ただ 始まりたくて 走った
I just wanted it to begin and started running.
遠く 暗がりにとまった
Stopped far off in the darkness.
それは 眩し過ぎた名前
That name shone far too brightly.
それは 優し過ぎる思い出もっと
That memory was far too kind, and yet...
近づけと 手を伸ばした
I reached out my hand, hoping to get closer.
思いがけず 結び合った
We unexpectedly bonded together.
ほら 今
Look, now
迷子は
The lost children
“僕等” になった
Have become "us".
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ
Shine bright!
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れて
Taking both frustration and affection with us,
おいで 風、夢、羽
Come on, wind, dreams, wings—
飛び立てるさ
We can take flight.
ささやかな祈りは 光
Our quiet prayers are a light,
終わりなき兆し
An endless sign.
君を見つけたこと
Finding you
胸を張れるよ
Is something we can be proud of.
まだ 頼りない予感を
Still carrying an uncertain premonition,
歌おう 恥ずかしそうなんて ないよ
Let's sing—there's nothing to be shy about.
誰も解けない イマジナリー
An imaginary bond no one can unravel,
いつかまた逢える おまじない
A spell to meet again someday.
あの日 ゼロに始まった ストーリー
The story that began from zero that day—
数え切れえない 言の葉 数のようじゃないさ
It's not just about counting words or thoughts.
ほら 今
Look, now
僕等を 一つと呼ぼう
Let's call "us" as one.
Parade, Parade, Parade!
美しいんだよ
It's so beautiful!
許し合える 刹那 夜は きらめく
In moments of mutual forgiveness, the night sparkles.
雨、晴れ、カレイド またとない空
Rain, clear skies, kaleidoscope—a one-of-a-kind sky.
相応しい旅路とは 君と歩くことさ
A fitting journey is walking together with you.
君と歩くことなんだ
It's walking alongside you!
ただ 今を聞けば おかえりって叫ぶよ
If we listen to the present, we'll shout "Welcome back!"
当たり前じゃないから
Because this isn't something to take for granted.
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ
Shine bright!
雲間から見おろすのは 君だ 僕だ
Looking down from between the clouds are you and me!
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ
Shine bright!
増やした想いと 愛しさを 連れておいで
Bringing along all our multiplied feelings and affection—
風、夢、羽 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings—we can take flight.
ささやかなないものばかり
Even if we only notice trivial things,
終わりなき気配し 君と飛び込んでゆく
We dive in together toward an endless presence.
素敵なスタートさ
What a wonderful start!
ここから これから
From here, from now on,
Our Bright Parade, Parade!
Parade, Parade, Parade!
告知ぱーとっ！
Announcement part!
え、この告知の後にもまだ歌うのでチャンネルはそのままで最後まで見てってください！
Wait, there's still more singing after this announcement, so keep it locked to the channel and watch until the very end!
そしてトレンド入りもありがとうございます！
And thank you so much for trending!
なんかご縁のありそうな方のホームランがすごいですおめでとうございます！
Apparently someone with a lucky connection hit an amazing home run—congratulations!
トレンドもありがとね！
Thank you for the trending too!
そしてですね、この告知パート、最後のほうにこよの配信でいいのか？というすごい告知もありますので、最後まで見てってください！
And also, in this announcement part, right near the end, there's an amazing announcement—is this really okay for Koyo's stream?—so please watch until the very end!
ではまず1つ目は冒頭でも言っていたこちら！
Now, first up is what I mentioned right at the start, this right here!
白衣こより 1stアルバム ダウンロード版は0時から販売開始されております概要欄からすでに飛べますのでゲットしてください！
Hakui Koyori's 1st Album digital download version goes on sale starting at midnight! You can already jump to it from the description box, so please go get your copy!
ですね、限定ボーナス トラック、
Right, the limited bonus track...
はい、はい、はい、はい、こんこよOPが
Yes, yes, yes, yes! The Konkoyo OP
入っているCD版もこの後21時からECサイトで受注販売もう一度行われますよ。
CD version containing it will be on sale again via EC site starting at 21:00 tonight!
カードもね入ってるんでこれじっくり読むのがすごい楽しいとみんなにご好評でした。
It includes cards too, so everyone praised how fun it is to read them carefully.
そして、通常版封入特典といたしまして、メインジャケットの表情違いのアナザー ジャケットカードがついてきまーす！
And as a standard version bonus, an alternate jacket card with a different expression from the main jacket will be included!
今回も数量限定でこよの直筆サインが入っているかも、なのでぜひまたお手に取ってもらえると嬉しいです。
This time too, it might have Koyori's handwritten signature in limited quantities, so we'd be happy if you could pick it up.
そして！白衣こよリ 誕生日記念グッズも出ます！
And! Hakui Koyori birthday commemorative goods are out too!
ドーン！
Ta-da!
まずは、ももこ先生に描いていただきました、
First, drawn by Momoko-sensei,
えー、オリジナルのライブ衣装みたいなすごい可愛いやつ、これあの画なんですけど、
um, a super cute original live outfit-like thing, this is an illustration, but...
に、えー、身を包んだこよりがライブをしてよーというね、素敵な2層アクリルパネル。
a wonderful two-layer acrylic panel of Koyori wrapped in it, doing a live performance.
これ2層になってるのでなんかせんきん感もあってすごいね、あのすごいかわいいです。
Since it's two layers, it has a sense of depth, and it's super, super cute.
ご褒美、絶対ゲットしてください！
Be sure to get your reward!
はい、フェスで欲しくなったよねみんな！こよ推しはっぴー！
Yes, you wanted it at the fest, right everyone? Kono-oshi happi!
まぁちょっとフェスエキスポ一週間前にお待ちしてましたけれども、えー、次回があるのか分かりませんけれども、なんかあるでしょ！
Well, we waited for it a week before Fest Expo, but um, there might be a next time, right? There's got to be something!
はい、次回のためにね、ぜひゲットしておいて、次の時に切れるようにしといてください。これ白衣っぽい柄になっててめちゃくちゃかわいいです。
Yes, for the next time, please be sure to get it so you can wear it then. It has a Hakui-like pattern and is super cute.
そして次！はい、去年出した制服衣装のとても可愛いぬいぐるみバッチ！
And next! Yes, the very cute plushie badge of the school uniform outfit released last year!
こちら今までのサイズ感と同じサイズ感になってますよ。くっそ可愛いのでゲットしてください。
This is in the same size as before. It's damn cute so please get it.
次！はい、最近ね、あのホロカやってる人も増えてきたので、こんこよカードケース作ってみました！
Next! Yes, recently, since more people are playing Holoca, I made a Konkoyo card case!
はい、ホロカって結構デッキ枚数が多いので、あのデッキ全部入るようにあのサイズ大きめに作っております。
Yes, Holoca has quite a large deck size, so we made the size larger so that all the cards fit in.
カードやってないよっていう人もですね、こちら、えー、あの開けて縫い場をさしとくとか、小物入れとか色々使えます。なんかめっっちゃ豪華なね、なんかあの合皮なのかな？みたいな感じになってますので、ゲットしてください。
For those who don't play cards, you can open it and put a pen, use it as a accessory pouch, etc. It has a super luxurious faux leather feel, so please get it.
そして、フルセット特典はこちら！
And, the full set bonus is here!
はい、限定です！で、直筆サイン、でそして、白衣、えーと白衣推しサインとメッセージ入りの、えーものが、えーついてきます。
Yes, it's limited! And, a handwritten autograph, and then, a Hakui, um, Hakui-oshi signed and message-included item is included.
そして、え、毎年恒例大好評！キミの誕生日を逆に お祝いするよ というASMRボイスがついてきます。
And, an annual huge hit! An ASMR voice where I celebrate your birthday in reverse is included.
これ本当に大好評でね、あのゲットしてなかった人だいたい後悔してますんで、自分の誕生日に聞くようにダウンロードしてずっと我慢して自分の誕生日で聞いてください。3月14日の人は1年我慢してください。よろしくお願いします。
This is really a huge hit, and people who didn't get it usually regret it, so please download it and wait until your birthday to listen to it on your birthday. People on March 14th, please wait a year. Thank you very much.
さらに今回フルセットこちら、ホロカもついてきまーす！やったー！今回のイラスト可愛すぎてホロカになるの最高すぎないか？推しカードついてきますよ。推しホロメンカードぜひゲットしてくださいね。ホロカ好きな皆さんもよろしくお願いします。
Furthermore, this time the full set includes Holoca! Yay! Isn't this illustration way too cute to be Holoca? It comes with an oshi card. Please definitely get the oshi holomen card. Thank you to everyone who loves Holoca too.
え、そしてね、カードオープンが21時5分になるようになってます。そう、あのみんなが慌てないように21時5分にカードオープンしますので、配信が終わる前にカードオープンしちゃうかもしれないんですけど、ちょっと余裕があるのでね、皆さんコメントのURLを要チェックしてください。
And, card open will be at 21:05. Yes, so that everyone doesn't rush, we'll open cards at 21:05, so you might open them before the stream ends, but there's a bit of time, so please check the comment URL.
え、そしてですね、このホロカさんからなんとココデールカードっていうね、映像告知をもらってますのでどうぞ！
And, from Holoca, we received a video announcement called "Kokodeiru Card," so here it is!
きたよ女子組
Finally here, the girls group,
ついにホロカにこよが来るよ！
Koyo is coming to Holoca!
新ブースターパック キュリアスユニバース 2025年6月20日発売！！
[Title: Curious Universe New Booster Pack Released June 20, 2025!!]
やったよ女子組！ついにホロカに来るしなんかすごいティザーPVあるよ！
We did it, girls group! Koyo is coming to Holoca and there's a super cool teaser PV!
ということで、なんと新ブースターパック「キュリアスユニバース」が、2025年6月20日に発売されるということが今ここで初めて世の中にちました。ここでいいの？マジで？と思いながら、
So, it was revealed for the very first time right here to the world that the new booster pack "Curious Universe" will be released on June 20, 2025. Thinking "Is this okay? Really?" while speaking...
こよちゃんがねすごい可愛いカードになってますし、最後になんかラプちゃんもいたんでラプちゃんもカード化するんじゃないですかね！
Koyo-chan is a super cute card, and since Lapu-chan was at the end, isn't Lapu-chan going to become a card too?
詳細は3月18日火曜日の朝7時からの朝コヨでさらに詳細情報をお届けさせてもらいますのでカード情報とかもなんかもらってました、確か。
Details will be brought to you in Asakoyo starting at 7:00 AM on Tuesday, March 18, and we got card info and stuff too, if I recall.
ので、お楽しみに！
So look forward to it!
それでは最後の曲お届けしたいと思います。ファーストアルバム「アイビーベベ」ファーストアルバムから「キミ = ♥」という白衣こよ初のかわいいEDMをお披露目します！
Now then, I'd like to deliver the final song. From the first album "Ivy Bebe", the first album's "Kimi = ♥", Hakui Koyori's very first cute EDM!
もっと 教えて
Tell me more,
もっと 答えてよ
Answer me more,
もっと 構って
Pay attention to me more,
解明してよ
And solve it!
この後、配信後にMVも公開しますので、
After this stream, the MV will also be released,
このまま飛んでプレミア公開ぜひ見ていってください。
so please head right over and check out the premiere!
そしてMV公開後メンバーシップ限定生配信もあります！
And after the MV premiere, there will be a membership-only live stream!
歌うし、
I'll be singing,
はいはいも、できちゃうかも？
and maybe even doing some 'hai-hai'?
あとね、このアルバムに入ってないオリジナル曲も
And also, original songs not on this album...
あるし、あのみんなが大好きなあの曲もあるし、
There are some, and that song everyone loves too...
まだまだ歌いますよってことで、スクショタイムとかもね
I'll be singing even more, so there'll be a screenshot time too,
やるのでぜひ見に来てください。
so please come check it out.
それでは、聴いてください。キミ＝♡
Now then, please listen to Kimi=♡.
もっと教えて
More, tell me,
もっと答えてよ
more, answer me,
もっと構って
more, care for me,
解かしてよ
and solve me.
きっと思い焦がれラブ
Surely, a love I yearn for.
脳内ずずっと君だって
My brain is always just about you,
問題ずずっと駄目だって
the problem is always that it's no good.
二進も三進昼夜逆転計算中です
Day and night in reverse, I'm calculating.
ずっと考えても君のことばっか
Even if I keep thinking, it's just about you.
ドキドキとトキメキを研究して
Researching excitement and heart-throbs,
恋の方程式はきっと解けるから
surely the equation of love will be solved.
もっと教えて
More, tell me,
もっと答えてよ
more, answer me,
もっと構って
more, care for me,
この気持ちもっと知りたい
I want to know more about this feeling,
君のこと… i want you 証明！
more about you... I want you, proof!
wanchu♪回ってアピールで
'Wanchu♪' spin and appeal,
wanwan♪構ってアピールで
'Wanwan♪' get attention and appeal,
wanchu♪回ってアピールで
'Wanchu♪' spin and appeal,
wanwan♪3回転
'Wanwan♪' 3 spins.
wanchu♪回ってアピールで引き寄せて
'Wanchu♪' spin and appeal, pull me closer,
きっと思い焦がれラブ
surely, a love I yearn for.
運命きっと君だって
Fate is surely just about you,
運勢きっと駄目だって
destiny is surely that it's no good.
二進も三進昼夜逆転計算中です
Day and night in reverse, I'm calculating.
ずっと考えても君のことばっか
Even if I keep thinking, it's just about you.
可愛いネイル・ヘアメイク研究して
Researching cute nails and hair and makeup,
君の心ずっと何%か分からない(T_T)
I don't know what percent of your heart is mine (T_T).
好きだよ
I like you.
言えたらもっと近くなれる？
If I could say it, could I get closer?
恥ずかしい
It's embarrassing.
甘えたい
I want to be spoiled.
自信ない
I have no confidence.
独り占めしたい
I want you all to myself.
嫌われたくない！
I don't want to be hated!
素直になりたい
I want to be honest.
重くないかな
Isn't it too heavy?
震える心それでも伝える
My trembling heart, even so, I'll tell you.
だってぼくはキミが大好き受け止めれてね
Because I love you so much, accept it, okay?
キミ＝♡
Kimi = ♡
answer違うのずっと欲しいのは…
Answer, that's not it, what I've always wanted is...
No.1なのはずっと欲しいのは…
Number one is what I've always wanted...
♡の本音
♡'s true feelings.
wanchu♪回ってアピールで
'Wanchu♪' spin and appeal,
wanwan♪構ってアピールで
'Wanwan♪' get attention and appeal,
wanchu♪回ってアピールで
'Wanchu♪' spin and appeal,
wanwan♪再現性
'Wanwan♪' reproducibility.
wanchu♪回ってアピールで見つけたよ
'Wanchu♪' spin and appeal, I found you.
i want you 証明！
I want you, proof!
wanchu♪回ってアピールで
'Wanchu♪' spin and appeal,
wanwan♪構ってアピールで
'Wanwan♪' get attention and appeal,
wanchu♪回ってアピールで
'Wanchu♪' spin and appeal,
wanwan♪3回転
'Wanwan♪' 3 spins.
wanchu♪回ってアピールで抱きしめて
'Wanchu♪' spin and appeal, hold me tight,
♡が止まらない
♡ won't stop.
この後、MV公開とメン限ライブ見に来てね！
After this, come watch the MV release and membership stream!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
うん、
Yeah,
ばいばーい！
bye-bye!
今日は今宵にとって
Today, for Koyori,
とても大切なライブを
such a very important live stream...
見に来てくれて、ありがとう！
Thank you for coming to watch!
直前の体調不良で心配かけちゃって
I'm sorry for making you worry with my sudden poor health right before,
ごめんね。
I'm sorry.
無事にできて
I'm so glad we pulled it off safely
本当によかったです！
and it went well!
ホロ活活動の第1歩目なライブと
How was the live performance, which is the first step of Hololive activities,
ファーストアルバム、どうだったかな？
and the 1st album?
少しでも君の心をくすぐる何かがあれば
I'd be happy if there was even a little something that tickled your heart,
嬉しいです。
I'd be glad.
あたり一面、全員女子くんの夢のソロライブに
I want to take everyone to my dream solo live filled entirely with Joshi-kun,
みんなを連れていきたい！
I want to take you all with me!
まだまだ1歩目、長い道のりだけど
It's still just the first step, a long road ahead,
ついてきてくれるかな？
but will you follow along with me?
一緒に歩いていこうね！
Let's walk together!
女子くん、大好きだよ！
Joshi-kun, I love you!
2025年3月15日 博衣こより
March 15, 2025 - Hakui Koyori